So, I'm seeing folks come back from Spain.
I mean, go back to Spain.
I'm seeing folks on the flotilla go back to the Netherlands.
And I'm not hearing anything about Greg, about other American veterans that are on the flotilla.
They're amplifying the harm that they're doing to Greta Thunberg, which is by design because they want to stir up the other sick sycophants.
You know, every time I think I know how depraved this place is, they find a new way to demonstrate it.
And when you see silence around our veterans in the flotilla, what you can assume is happening is that there is probably some backdoor conversing happening.
But it's happening backdoor because they still want to protect the relationship with Israel.
Like, that's more important.
And not enough folks are understanding that if that's more important than protecting you or than even giving you morale, then what are we doing?
Like, I saw someone, I saw a black man arguing in the comments of Know Your Caribbean's post saying, this is my government.
No, it's not, this ain't none of the people's government, not even these white folks that think it's their government.
This is a billionaire's government.
Pacifically, billionaire government.
I am deeply disturbed.
And we have to keep amplifying, calling, emailing, and physically showing up at these embassies, at these offices here in the United States in particular,
to demand that there is actual effort done to make sure that our people come home safely.
Our people who left on a humanitarian aid mission, an unarmed humanitarian aid mission where it is being touted and flaunted that they are being treated as terrorists.
But then, surprise, because Joe Biden and Kamala Harris were calling Columbia University students protesting the use of their money and their tuition being used in a genocide, they called them terrorists.
So, I'm trying to wrap it up in my head what to do, and I'm genuinely just furious on a level of, I don't even know.
I know, Huri, this is not something just happening in our phones.
This is not something just happening in our phones.